life-enthusiast.com 2012-11-17

# Life Enthusiast: Information and Help

We assume that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust and want you to feel confident in our services and security as it relates to your personal information. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Life Enthusiast Co-op website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. 

**What Personal Information About Customers Does Life Enthusiast Co-op Gather?**

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Life Enthusiast Co-op. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, fulfilling orders, customizing future shopping for you, improving our store features, and communication with you. 
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our website. For example, like many web sites, we sometimes use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our website. 
  * **E-mail Communications:** To help us make e-mails more productive to improve service and your shopping experience, we sometimes send you newsletters of our services and products, notifications of changes to our policies, and order confirmations. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, other than order notifications and receipts, please adjust your "Subscription" preferences by logging into your account. 

**What About Cookies?**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifier text files that we transfer to your computers hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.

**Does Life Enthusiast Co-op Canada Share the Information It Receives?**

We respect your privacy and appreciate your business. At no time do we ever provide your account contact or payment information to any third party vendor, associate or service provider unless absolutely neccessary in order to complete your transaction and order.

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you provide to us for purchasing of our products or services. We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer by clicking the "log off" link located in the side menu.

**Which Information Can I Access?**

Life Enthusiast Co-op gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with us for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit Life Enthusiast Co-op, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the province of our local province. If you have any concern about privacy of your personal information as used and collected within our website, please send us a thorough description by clicking on the "Contact Us" link on the side menu, and we will try to resolve it. 

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers. 

**Information You Give Us**

You provide most such information when you search, buy, order, post reviews, or other methods of communication via our website or email to Life Enthusiast Co-op. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers, and credit card information.

**Automatic Information**

For security purposes Life Enthusiast Co-op sometimes collects and analyzes the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, and to our website. This is done for your protection for tracking purposes in the unfortunate event that someone gains access to your personal or financial information and opens an account, or makes purchases under your name.

## Security and Credit Card Safety

### When you place an order with us, we use a secure server.

We use software that encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. This means that no prying eyes will be able to see your personal information while it is in transit to us, because it will be encrypted.

This encryption software is called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), and is the industry standard. It is the best encryption method available today for confident and secure online commerce transactions.

Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. All payment information is kept on a stand-alone computer behind a firewall.

##  Still Too Nervous About Placing Your Order On-Line?

That's alright... you can also provide us with your order and payment information by telephone, toll-free at 1-866-543-3388.
